I got those green green eyes
For blue nights
Mmm
All of the sounds that move and rise
Yeah, I've grown to know
Mmm
But I'm letting it
Yeah I'm letting it go
Yeah my mind is on fire, mind is on fire
Said as hard as I try, still can't rewind
Again, and again, and again to make time
Yeah and I'm so scared the change I thought we've made gets washed away
And all the ways you touch me
Under the stars I always try to trace
But if we never find a better place?
I don't wanna go
Just to let you know
You've got those grey grey eyes
For a sunrise
Mmm
All of that rain that fell a while
We could hum to
Mmm
But I'm letting it
Yeah I'm letting it go
My mind is on fire, mind is on fire
As hard as I try, still can't rewind
I can't and I can't turn back time
Yeah and I'm so scared the change I thought we've made gets washed away
And all the ways you touch me
Under the stars I always try to trace
What if we never find a place?
I don't wanna go, no
Just to let you know
I'm already home